Along the ancient path of the Monongahela River,
沿着古老的莫农加希拉河，
Braddock, Pennsylvania sits in the eastern region of Allegheny County,
宾夕法尼亚州的布拉多克，坐落在阿利根尼县的东部地区，
approximately nine miles outside of Pittsburgh.
距匹兹堡市中心大约九英里。
An industrial suburb,
作为工业市郊，
Braddock is home to Andrew Carnegie's first steel mill,
布拉多克开设有安德鲁卡耐基的第一座钢厂，
the Edgar Thomson Works.
即埃德加托马斯工厂。
Operating since 1875,
它于1875年投入运营，
it is the last functioning steel mill in the region.
如今是该地区最后一个还在运转的钢厂。
For 12 years, I have produced collaborative portraits,
12年来，我制作了群体人物，
still lifes, landscapes and aerial views
静态生活，风景地貌，俯瞰图景，
in order to build a visual archive to address the intersection
为的是建立一个视觉档案，
of the steel industry,
以凸显钢铁工业，
the environment,
环境，
and the health care system's impact on the bodies of my family and community.
以及医疗卫生系统的交叉点对我家人和社区的影响。
The tradition and grand narrative of Braddock
对布拉多克传统且宏大的的描述
is mostly comprised of stories of industrialists and trade unions.
多是由工业家和工会的故事组成。
Currently, the new narrative about Braddock,
如今，作为没落工业地区重新振兴的代表，
a poster child for Rust Belt revitalization,
对布拉多克的新描述，
is a story of urban pioneers discovering a new frontier.
是城市先驱开拓前沿的故事。
Mass media has omitted the fact that Braddock is predominantly black.
大量媒体忽略了布拉多克的居民以黑人为主的事实。
Our existence has been co-opted, silenced and erased.
我们的存在被消融、被压制、被抹去了。
Fourth generation in a lineage of women,
作为家族中第四代女性，
I was raised under the protection and care of Grandma Ruby,
我在祖母露比的保护和照顾下
off 8th Street at 805 Washington Avenue.
成长在华盛顿大街805号第八街道旁。
She worked as a manager for Goodwill.
她曾是Goodwill的经理。
Mom was a nurse's aid.
我母亲是一位看护助理。
She watched the steel mills close and white flight to suburban developments.
她见证了钢厂倒闭，白人来到市郊发展创业。
By the time my generation walked the streets,
到了我这一代漫步在街道上时，
disinvestment at the local, state and federal level,
地方、州和联邦政府的撤资，
eroded infrastructure,
损毁的公共设施，
and the War on Drugs dismantled my family and community.
针对毒品的打击，拆散了我的家人和社区。
Grandma Ruby's stepfather Gramps
祖母露比的继父格兰普斯
was one of few black men to retire from Carnegie's mill with his pension.
是少数从卡耐基钢厂拿到养老金退休的黑人之一。
He worked in high temperatures,
他工作在高温下，
tearing down and rebuilding furnaces, cleaning up spilt metal and slag.
拆除再重组熔炉，清除溢出的金属和炉渣。
The history of a place is written on the body and the landscape.
一个地方的历史是书写在人体和市容上的。
Areas of heavy truck traffic,
这些地区有重型卡车来来往往，
exposure to benzene and atomized metals,
弥漫着苯和雾化金属物，
risk cancer and lupus.
癌症和狼疮的风险无处不在。
One hundred twenty-three licensed beds, 652 employees,
一百二十三张获批的床位，六百五十二名雇员，
rehabilitation programs decimated.
善后项目大幅度减少。
A housing discrimination lawsuit against Allegheny County
一桩针对阿利根尼县的住房歧视诉讼
removed where the projects Talbot Towers once stood.
移除了曾经伫立的塔尔博特塔。
Recent rezoning for more light industry has since appeared.
最近，为了更多的轻工业发展，出现了分区再规划。
Google Maps and Google Earth pixelations conceal the flammable waste
谷歌地图和谷歌地球隐去了易燃废料，
being used to squeeze the Bunn family off their home and land.
它们曾被用于将邦恩家族排挤出他们的家园和土地。
In 2013, I chartered a helicopter
在2013年，我租用了一架直升飞机，
with my cameras to document this aggressive dispossession.
带着我的相机去记录这些侵略性的土地剥夺。
In flight, my observation reveals thousands of plastic white bundles
在飞机上，我的视野中出现了成千上万捆的白色塑料，
owned by a conservation industry
它们属于一家环保企业，
that claims it's eco-friendly
声称这些塑料是环保的，
and recycles millions of tires
而且是循环利用了数百万的轮胎
to preserve people's lives
去保障人民的生活，
and to improve people's lives.
并提升生活的品质。
My work spirals from the micro to the macro level,
我的工作从微观层面提升到宏观层面，
excavating hidden histories.
挖掘隐藏在背后的故事。
Recently, at the Seattle Art Museum,
最近，在西雅图艺术博物馆，
Isaac Bunn and I mounted this exhibition,
艾萨克邦恩和我安排了这个展览，
and the exhibition was used as a platform to launch his voice.
展览被当作让他发声的一个平台。
Through reclamation of our narrative,
通过不断丰富修正我们的描述，
we will continue to fight historic erasure and socioeconomic inequality.
我们将继续为历史的磨灭和社会经济的不平等而战斗。
Thank you.
谢谢。
(Applause)
（掌声）